{
  "level": 4,
  "unit": 1,
  "vocabulary": [
    {
      "week": "12",
      "words": [
        {
          "prompt": "To ___________ means to make different or change.",
          "answer": "alter"
        },
        {
          "prompt": "To ___________ means to fall down or cave in.",
          "answer": "collapse"
        },
        {
          "prompt": "A ___________ is a difficult or dangerous situation.",
          "answer": "crisis"
        },
        {
          "prompt": "___________ is great damage or ruin.",
          "answer": "destruction"
        },
        {
          "prompt": "A ___________ is something that can cause harm or injury.",
          "answer": "hazard"
        },
        {
          "prompt": "Something ___________ is very harsh or serious.",
          "answer": "severe"
        },
        {
          "prompt": "Something ___________ is of a great amount or size.",
          "answer": "substantial"
        },
        {
          "prompt": "___________ means not able to tell beforehand.",
          "answer": "unpredictable"
        }
      ]
    },
    {
      "week": "34",
      "words": [
        {
          "prompt": "To be ___________ means to be responsible.",
          "answer": "accountable"
        },
        {
          "prompt": "To ___________ means to give oneâ€™s opinion or to inform.",
          "answer": "advise"
        },
        {
          "prompt": "To act ___________ means to try anything to change a hopeless situation.",
          "answer": "desperately"
        },
        {
          "prompt": "If you ___________ , you waited or stopped, especially because of feeling unsure.",
          "answer": "hesitated"
        },
        {
          "prompt": "To be ___________ means to be made to feel ashamed or foolish.",
          "answer": "humiliated"
        },
        {
          "prompt": "An ___________ is a person or thing that stirs the mind, feelings, or imagination.",
          "answer": "inspiration"
        },
        {
          "prompt": "To have ___________ is to have respect for oneself.",
          "answer": "self-esteem"
        },
        { "prompt": "___________ means 'uneasily.'", "answer": "uncomfortably" }
      ]
    },
    {
      "week": "5",
      "words": [
        {
          "prompt": "Something that is ___________ is new or done in a new way.",
          "answer": "innovative"
        },
        {
          "prompt": "To be ___________ is to be sympathetic.",
          "answer": "compassionate"
        },
        {
          "prompt": "An ___________ is something difficult or important that a person plans or tries to do.",
          "answer": "enterprise"
        },
        {
          "prompt": "To be ___________ is to be extraordinary.",
          "answer": "exceptional"
        },
        {
          "prompt": "___________ are money that is ready for use.",
          "answer": "funds"
        },
        {
          "prompt": "A ___________ is a series of actions performed when making or doing something.",
          "answer": "process"
        },
        {
          "prompt": "A ___________ is a fixed way or method of doing something.",
          "answer": "routine"
        },
        {
          "prompt": "An ___________ is something someone decides to do or start.",
          "answer": "undertaking"
        }
      ]
    }
  ]
}
